## **Curriculum Vitae**

N: Rubenia Noronha

A: 12 The Drive, Hunters Run, Dublin 15 / T: +353 83 3401615

E: <u>rubeniadsn@hotmail.com</u> Languages: Portuguese (mother tongue), English (intermediate)

Irish passport/citizenship

Full license/Car owner

\_\_\_\_\_

I have recently returned to Ireland where I Lived and worked for 10 years previously and now looking for new opportunities here.

For the past 7 years in Brazil I worked as a dental clinic assistant (working the reception, general management of the clinic and also assisting the dentist during procedures).

During my previous residence in Ireland I worked for the Kepak Group. During which time I was able to move across functions gaining a vast number of experiences some of which are in quality control, line worker, packing, canteen etc.

Before coming to Ireland the first time, I used to own a small business in Brazil.

In each of my employments I stayed for a number of years and undertook multiple responsibilities which shows how reliable, loyal and flexible I am. Some of my other strengths are fast learner, resilience, patience and good customer service.

-----

## **Career History**

General Operative, Freshway Food Production; Dublin, Ireland; From November 2020 to present.

- Packaging product with great care to protect quality and minimize damage and waste.
- Attaching box-end labels to finished goods crates/boxes as required
- Responsible for the production and/or packing a variety of products to the agreed standards efficiently

Office Cleaning Operative, Servest Group Limited; Dublin, Ireland; From January 2020 to March 2020

- General Office Cleaning duties
- Clean floors, surfaces and bathrooms using predefined cleaning methods and procedures while ensuring hygiene and health and safety regulations are adhered to at all times;
- Job terminated due the COVID Pandemic

**Dentist Clinic general assistant/receptionist,** Joana Passos Pontes Clinic; *Fortaleza, Brazil; From 2012 - 2019* 

- General Dentist Clinic reception work (book appointments, answer customer queries, admin work, managing cashflow, ordering materials, cleaning)
- Handling of materials for the procedures (sterilizing, packing, preparation)
- Assist dentist during procedures

General operative - cross-functions, Kepak Group; Dublin, Ireland; From 2000 - 2009

- Quality Control of Products
- Packaging of products
- Line worker
- Canteen assistant

Owner, Jurema Sawmill and Dikasa Construction Materials Ltd; Caucaia, Brazil; From 1995 – 2000

• General duties of running a small business, Admin, Buyer, Sales, Customer Services

## **Education & Training**

- Certificate in Dental Clinic Assistant, Senac (Fortaleza-Brazil,1991)
- Concluded Secondary School (leaving cert), School Oliveira Paiva (Fortaleza-Brazil, 1987)
- Manual Handling Certificate